Georgy Savva

Summary

Computer science student with seven years of professional software engineering experience and self-taught foundations in machine learning. Interested in machine learning research, specifically reinforcement learning.

Skills

Python | Deep Learning | Reinforcement Learning | NLP | Computer Vision | PyTorch | TensorFlow | SQL | Distributed Systems | Systems Design | Docker | Go

Education

Russian University of Cooperation, 2019 - 2021 Bachelor of Science - Computer Science

National Research Nuclear University MEPhl. 2014 - 2016 Bachelor of Science - Cybersecurity

Courses & Certifications

- Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and Optimization - DeepLearning.AI GPA: 98/100
- Generative AI with Large Language Models DeepLearning.AI GPA: 91/100
- Structuring Machine Learning Projects DeepLearning.AI GPA: 87/100
- Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and Optimization - DeepLearning.AI GPA: 98/100
- Neural Networks and Deep Learning DeepLearning.Al GPA: 97/100
- Mathematics for Machine Learning: Linear Algebra Imperial College London GPA: 96/100
- Mathematics for Machine Learning: Multivariate Calculus Imperial College London GPA: 96/100
- YC Summer Startup School Y Combinator
- Sports Programming National Research Nuclear University MEPhl

Professional Experience

Senior Software Engineer, Raylu — (Oct 2023 - Present)

An LLM-powered software personalization tool.

Technical Co-Founder, Scifind — (Jul 2022 - May 2023)

A troubleshooting platform for bioscientists.

Senior Software Engineer, IOTA — (Jan 2021 - Jul 2022)

An open-source, feeless distributed ledger technology.

Senior Software Engineer, Elsa — (Jan 2020 - Jan 2021)

An Al-powered app that improves your English pronunciation.

Senior Software Engineer, Localistico — (Jun 2019 - Jan 2020)

An aggregator that helps businesses, such as shops and restaurants, manage and keep in sync all their locations on major platforms such as Google Maps, Facebook, TripAdvisor, Yelp, and Foursquare.

Software Engineer, Edwin.ai — (*Mar 2017 - May 2019*)

An Al-powered service preparing students for standardized English tests such as TOEFL and TOEIC.

Software Engineer, Snaappy — (*Jun 2016 - Mar 2017*)

An instant messaging service popular among teens in Eastern Europe.

Projects

Open-Source Library Scany — (May 2020 - Present)

Created an open-source library to map data from the database into Go objects. It has over a thousand stars on GitHub and is used by thousands of companies and individual developers: https://github.com/georgysavva/scany.

Fintech Project — (December 2015 - June 2016)

Joined a Computer Science faculty member in a fintech project at the National Research Nuclear University MEPhI, where I helped rewrite the backend for a payment system.

Languages

English — Proficient speaker

Russian — Native speaker